{"test_questions": [[{"question": "When parallel resistors are of three different values, which has the greatest power loss?", "opta": "The smallest resistance", "optb": "The largest resistance", "optc": "They have the same power loss.", "optd": "Voltage and resistance values are needed.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the product-over-sum result of 150 and 6800?", "opta": "150", "optb": "146.7", "optc": "0.006", "optd": "6800", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The voltage across any branch of a parallel circuit:", "opta": "varies as the total current varies", "optb": "is inversely proportional to total circuit resistance", "optc": "is equally applied to all branch conductances", "optd": "is dropped in proportion to each branch resistance", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total power loss if 2 k and 1 k parallel-connected resistors have an IT of 3 mA?", "opta": "6 W", "optb": "36 W", "optc": "6 mW", "optd": "36 mW", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What happens to total resistance in a circuit with parallel resistors if one of them opens?", "opta": "It increases.", "optb": "It halves.", "optc": "It remains the same.", "optd": "It decreases.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Components that connect in parallel form:", "opta": "branches", "optb": "open circuits", "optc": "short circuits", "optd": "a voltage divider", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A parallel circuit differs from a series circuit in that a parallel circuit has", "opta": "no path for current flow", "optb": "fewer paths for current flow", "optc": "one path for current flow", "optd": "more than one path for current flow", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In the given circuit, Channel 1 of the stereo amplifier outputs 12 V to the speakers. How much total current is the amplifier providing to the speakers?", "opta": "0 A", "optb": "1.5 A", "optc": "3 A", "optd": "More information is needed to find the total current provided to the speakers.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If two parallel-connected resistors dissipate 6 watts and 10 watts of power, then what is the total power loss?", "opta": "3.75 watts", "optb": "4 watts", "optc": "16 watts", "optd": "60 watts", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which component is shorted?", "opta": "R1", "optb": "R2", "optc": "R3", "optd": "R4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What would these meter readings indicate about the circuit in the given circuit?Meter Readings: I = 7.6 mA, V = 12 V", "opta": "R1 is open.", "optb": "R2 is open.", "optc": "The fuse is open.", "optd": "The circuit is operating normally.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In the given circuit, Channel 1 of the stereo amplifier outputs 12 V to the speakers. How much total power is the amplifier delivering to the speakers?", "opta": "0 W", "optb": "18 W", "optc": "36 W", "optd": "More information is needed to find the total power delivered to the speakers.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If a 1 k and a 2 k resistor are parallel-connected across a 12 V supply, how much current is received by the 2 k resistor?", "opta": "4 mA", "optb": "6 mA", "optc": "8 mA", "optd": "12 mA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does VS equal in the given circuit?", "opta": "0 V", "optb": "9 V", "optc": "27 V", "optd": "More information is needed to find VS.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The current through R1 will be:", "opta": "128 mA", "optb": "88 mA", "optc": "48 mA", "optd": "2.2 mA", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The voltage read by the voltmeter will be:", "opta": "24 V", "optb": "12 V", "optc": "6 V", "optd": "4 V", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which component is of the wrong value?", "opta": "R1", "optb": "R2", "optc": "R3", "optd": "R4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does I3 equal in the given circuit?", "opta": "5 mA", "optb": "45 mA", "optc": "50 mA", "optd": "100 mA", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total power of the circuit?", "opta": "2.2 W", "optb": "4.2 W", "optc": "6.2 W", "optd": "8.2 W", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What are the individual values of two parallel resistors whose RT is 8 ohms, when one has double the resistance of the other?", "opta": "2.7 ohms and 5.3 ohms", "optb": "8 ohms and 16 ohms", "optc": "10 ohms and 20 ohms", "optd": "12 ohms and 24 ohms", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When a parallel 5 k resistor and a 25 k resistor have a 10 V supply, what is the total power loss?", "opta": "2.4 mW", "optb": "3.3 mW", "optc": "24 mW", "optd": "33 mW", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a parallel resistive circuit:", "opta": "there is more than one current path between two points", "optb": "the voltage applied divides between the branches", "optc": "the total branch power exceeds the source power", "optd": "the total circuit conductance is less than the smallest branch conductance", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total resistance?", "opta": "7 k", "optb": "1 k", "optc": "706", "optd": "353", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Kirchhoff's current law for parallel circuits states that the:", "opta": "sum of all branch voltages equals zero", "optb": "total circuit resistance is less than the smallest branch resistor", "optc": "sum of currents into a junction is equal to the difference of all the branch currents", "optd": "sum of the total currents flowing out of a junction equals the sum of the total currents flowing into that junction", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which component is open?", "opta": "R1", "optb": "R2", "optc": "R3", "optd": "R4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What would these meter readings indicate about the circuit in the given circuit?Meter Readings: I = 0 mA, V = 0 V", "opta": "R1 is open.", "optb": "R2 is open.", "optc": "The fuse is open.", "optd": "The circuit is operating normally.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If 550 mA of current leaves a node that had 250 mA entering from one branch, how much current would enter from the other?", "opta": "250 mA", "optb": "300 mA", "optc": "550 mA", "optd": "800 mA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What would these meter readings indicate about the circuit in the given circuit?Meter Readings: I = 10 mA, V = 12 V", "opta": "R1 is open.", "optb": "R2 is open.", "optc": "The fuse is open.", "optd": "The circuit is operating normally.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does RT equal in the given circuit?", "opta": "90", "optb": "180", "optc": "200", "optd": "1.8 k", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What procedure should be followed when troubleshooting with an ammeter or voltmeter?", "opta": "Short the leads and adjust.", "optb": "Check the meter\u0092s external power supply.", "optc": "Start with the highest scale and adjust down to a lower scale.", "optd": "Start with the lowest scale and adjust up to a higher scale.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A parallel circuit is also used as a divider for:", "opta": "conductance", "optb": "voltage", "optc": "power", "optd": "current", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is RT for a 12 k, a 4 k, and a 3 k resistor in parallel?", "opta": "1.5 k", "optb": "2 k", "optc": "6.3 k", "optd": "19 k", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total resistance of four 1 k parallel-connected resistors?", "opta": "200 ohms", "optb": "250 ohms", "optc": "400 ohms", "optd": "4 kilohms", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which are the better test devices used to isolate a suspected open component within a parallel circuit?", "opta": "a voltmeter or an ohmmeter", "optb": "neither an ammeter nor a voltmeter", "optc": "a wattmeter or a voltmeter", "optd": "an ammeter or an ohmmeter", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does P2 equal in the given circuit?", "opta": "45 mW", "optb": "405 mW", "optc": "450 mW", "optd": "900 mW", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does R1 equal in the given circuit?", "opta": "90", "optb": "180", "optc": "200", "optd": "1.8 k", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total resistance?", "opta": "1.045 k", "optb": "1.545 k", "optc": "2.045 k", "optd": "2.545 k", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is RT for fifteen 2 M resistors all connected in parallel?", "opta": "133 k", "optb": "300 k", "optc": "750 k", "optd": "30 M", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is considered to be the common reference for a parallel circuit?", "opta": "Voltage", "optb": "Current", "optc": "Power", "optd": "Resistance", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}